Finding Aid of the Midwest Archives Conference Records, 1972-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Midwest Archives Conference Records, 1972-2014
Midwest Archives Conference
UWM Manuscript Collection 194
Accession 2013-051
42.1 cubic ft. (112 boxes) 1,088 digital files (354 MB) plus additions of .8 cubic ft. (2 boxes)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
This collection contains records of the Midwest Archives Conference (MAC) from the organization's founding in 1972 until the present. Included are records from MAC's presidents, secretaries and treasurers, council, committees, meetings, publications, public information officers, and audio-visual materials and memorabilia. The collection documents activities of this regional archival association, particularly issues of concern, such as the appointment of the Archivist of the United States, developments in the field of archives, and the organization's bi-annual meetings. Publications include complete sets of MAC newsletters (1973-present) and journal, the Midwestern Archivist (1976-1991) and Archival Issues (1992-present).
The Midwest Archives Conference (MAC) was organized at a June 1972 meeting attended by 111 interested professionals. Since its founding the organization has grown into one of the largest regional archival associations in the country. Members include archivists, manuscript curators, librarians, records managers, historians, and allied professionals working in historical societies; local, state, and federal archives; college and university archives; religious archives; health science archives; and corporate archives. The MAC region covers thirteen states: Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri, Nebraska, North Dakota, South Dakota, Ohio, and Wisconsin.
MAC holds an annual meeting in spring and a symposium in the fall in cities throughout the region. The organization publishes a quarterly newsletter and a professional journal.
MAC Presidents
1972-1975 Archie Motley
1975-1977 Jacqueline (Mrs. Philip S.) Haring
1977-1979 Mary Ann Bamberger
1979-1981 Nicholas Burckel
1981-1983 Patrick Quinn
1983-1985 James Fogerty
1985-1987 Mary Janzen
1987-1989 William Maher
1989-1991 Nancy Lankford
1991-1993 Valerie Gerrard Browne
1993-1995 J. Frank Cook
1995-1997 Mark Greene
1997-1999 Pat Michaelis
1999-2001 Frank Boles
2001-2003 Cheri Thies
2003-2005 Steve McShane
2005-2007 Elisabeth Wittman
2007-2009 Dennis Meissner
2009-2011 Tanya Zanish-Belcher
2011-2013 Ellen Swain
2013-2015 Amy Cooper Cary
For more information, please visit the Midwest Archives Conference Web site at: www.midwestarchives.org.
Scope and content notes for each record subgroup and/or series are included in the contents list.
Acronyms Used in This Finding Aid
Acronym Expansion
ARMA
Association of Records Managers and Administrators
MARAC
Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference
NEH
National Endowment for the Humanities
NHPRC
National Historical Publications and Records Commission
NUCMC
National Union Catalog of Manuscript Collections
SAA
Society of American Archivists
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
UWM Manuscript Collection 194: Records, 1972-2014
The collection is arranged into the following record subgroups, and, unless specified, alphabetically by folder title and then chronologically within each record group.
President, 1972-2013
Archie Motley
Jacqueline (Mrs. Philip S.) Haring
Mary Ann Bamberger
Nicholas Burckel
Patrick Quinn
James Fogerty
Mary Janzen
William Maher
Nancy Lankford
Valerie Gerrard Browne
Frank Cook
Mark Greene
Pat Michaelis
Frank Boles
Cheri Thies
Steve McShane
Elisabeth Wittman
Dennis Meissner
Tanya Zanish-Belcher
Ellen Swain
Vice Presidents, 1996-2011
Elisabeth Wittman
Sherry Williams
Paul Eisloeffel
Tanya Zanish-Belcher
Doug Bicknese
Mark Shelstad
Secretary and Treasurer, 1972-2013
Secretary and Treasurer, 1972-1990
Secretary, 1974-2013
Treasurer, 1994-2008
Council, 1972-2013
Committees, 1972-2010
Meetings, 1972-2014
Publications, 1972-2010
Calendar, 1992-2001
Journal, 1976-2014
Newsletter, 1973-2010
Journal Editorial Board, 1974-1999
Administrative Files, 1974-1999
Accepted Journal Articles, 1974-1998
Newsletter Editorial Board, 1972-2001
Public Information Officer, 1986-1990
Audio-Visual Materials, 1972-2004
Photographs and Slides, 1973-1997
Audio and Videocassettes, 1974-1986
Memorabilia, 1972-2004
The collection contains one additional accession.
Accession 2013-051: Archival Issues Editorial Board Records, 2011-2014
A spreadsheet with file-level information on the electronic records is available in the Archives Department. The spreadsheet contains information on file title (where applicable), author, dates created, modified, file formats, file size, and number of pages. Additional technical metadata is available; consult an archivist for more information.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
Society of American Archivists Records UWM Manuscript Collection 172
Administrative/Restriction Information
The Accepted Journal Article Files are restricted for 15 years from the date of the review. Some of the Journal Editorial Board files which pertain to manuscript reviews are also restricted for 15 years. Access to these records will be available only to the current MAC Editorial Board chair.
Patrons must use digital access copies of the original VHS recordings.
There are no access restrictions on the remainder of the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The Midwest Archives Conference donated its records to the UWM Archives in January 2003. At that time, the collection was transferred from Northwestern University in Evanston, Illinois to the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (accession 2002-070). The UWM Archives regularly receives additions to the collection. Information about these additions is available on request.
As of April 4, 2014, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Software used to access the files includes Microsoft Office 2007, Firefox v. 21.0, and Adobe Reader XI.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Microsoft Word Document 97-2003 [.doc]
Microsoft Word for Windows 2007 onwards [.docx]
Hypertext Markup Language [.html]
Acrobat PDF 1.2-1.6 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Windows Bitmap [.bmp]
Graphics Interchange Format [.gif]
JPEG File Interchange Format [.jpg]
Lotus WordPro Document [.lwp]
Microsoft Outlook Email Message [.msg]
Microsoft Powerpoint Document [.ppt]
Microsoft Powerpoint for Windows 2007 onwards [.pptx]
Microsoft Publisher [.pub]
Rich Text Format [.rtf]
Tagged Image File Format [.tiff]
Plain Text File [.txt]
Windows Metafile Image [.wmf]
WordPerfect for MS-DOS/Windows Document [.wpd]
Microsoft Works Word Processor 5-6 [.wps]
Microsoft Excel 97 Workbook [.xls]
Microsoft Excel for Windows 2007 onwards [.xlsx]
Deaccession Information
With the permission of Council, Christel Maass removed from the collection on July 1, 2005 all rejected Midwestern Archivist and Archival Issues manuscripts and all accepted manuscripts that were withdrawn prior to publication. These were originally housed in boxes 92 through 97.
Contents List
- Records, 1972-2014, UWM Manuscript Collection 194; 42.1 cubic ft. (112 boxes) 1,083 digital files (171 MB)
  - 1. President, 1972-2013
    This record subgroup contains the files of MAC presidents, as well as some supporting documentation that precedes an individual's term in office. Files document MAC's founding in 1972 and Archie Motley's term as the first president of the organization. They also include records of subsequent presidents, such as correspondence; committee files; bi-annual meetings files; Council meeting materials; membership statistics, surveys, and questionnaires; and newsletter and journal files. The subgroup also documents issues of concern to the profession, such as the appointment of the Archivist of the United States, archival education, certification, MAC scholarships and awards, and developments in the field.
    - Archie Motley
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
      - Fall Meeting, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Fall Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Fall Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Membership and Conference Attendance, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - New Projects Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - SAA Council Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Spring Meeting, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Spring Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Spring Meeting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Spring Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Jacqueline (Mrs. Philip S.) Haring
      - Conservation Center, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Council Meeting Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Duties and Privileges Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Editorial Board, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Emeritus (Honorary), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Membership Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Newsletter, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Nominating Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Program Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - SAA Activities, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - SAA Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Special Seminar on Conservation, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Special Seminars, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Spring Meeting, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mary Ann Bamberger
      - Archives Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Committee Guidelines, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Committee on Personnel Matters, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Conservation Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Council Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
      - Education Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Emeritus Membership, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - International Council on Archives, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Iowa Historical Materials Preservation Society, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - LCOMM (Library Council of Metropolitan Milwaukee), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Legislation, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Liability Insurance Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Membership Analysis Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Midwestern Archivist, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - NHPRC, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Nominating Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Program Analysis Committee, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Spring 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Spring/Fall 1978, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
      - Resolutions, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - SAA, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Nicholas Burckel
      - Archives Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Archivist of the United States, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Coalition to Save Our Documentary Heritage, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Committee Guidelines, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Committee on Personnel Matters, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Committee on Regional Archival Activity, 1979-1981 (Box 5)
      - Conservation Task Force, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence
        - Alphabetical, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - Chronological, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
      - Council, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
      - Education Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Emeritus Membership, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Liability Insurance Task Force, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        - Fall 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - Fall 1983, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Spring 1979, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Membership Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Membership Questionnaire, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Midwestern Archivist, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - NHPRC Reauthorization, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Nominating Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Officers, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1980, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
        - Spring 1980, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        - Spring 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
        - Spring 1982, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Regional Archival Networks Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Resolutions, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Softball Challenge, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Patrick Quinn
      - Archives Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Committee Guidelines, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Conservation Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence
        - Incoming, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
        - Outgoing, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
      - Correspondence to Council Members, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Council Meeting Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Education Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Educational Goals Task Force, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Governing Structures Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1981, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
        - Fall 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
        - Spring 1981, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Spring 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1983, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Membership Report, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Membership Survey, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Midwestern Archivist Editorial Board, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - National Conference on Regional Archival Networks, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - NEH Grant, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Newsletter, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - NHPRC, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nominating Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Program Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - James Fogerty
      - Constitution/Bylaws Committee, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Council Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Data Base Task Force, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Development Task Force, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Education Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1983, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1985, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1983, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        - Spring 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Meeting
        - Fall 1986, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
        - Fall 1987, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
        - Fall 1988, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Membership Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Midwestern Archivist Editorial Board, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - NHPRC, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Nominating Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1983, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - Fall 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - Fall 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Spring 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Spring 1985, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Mary Janzen
      - Archives and Society Task Force, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Archivist of the United States, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Certification, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Committee Guidelines, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Council 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
      - Development Task Force, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Education Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Emeritus Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1985, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
        - Spring 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Membership Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Membership Questionnaire, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Midwestern Archivist Editorial Board, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Nominating Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - President's Award, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - President's Award, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1986, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - Spring 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - SAA Committee on Regional Archival Activity, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - William Maher
      - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Archivist of the United States, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Certification, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Council Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5-8)
      - Development Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Education Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Emeritus Membership, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Financial Resources, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Graphics, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Spring 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Meeting
        - Fall 1987, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - Fall 1988, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - Fall 1989, 1985-1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Fall 1989, Michigan Archival Association Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - Spring 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - Spring 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Membership Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Midwestern Archivist Editorial Board, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
      - Nominating Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Officers and Council, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - President's Award, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Program Committee, Spring 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Public Information Officer, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - SAA Committee on Regional Archival Activity, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - SAA Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - SAA MAC Mixer, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - SAA/MAC Joint Membership Solicitation in Iowa, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - State and Local Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Nancy Lankford
      - Council, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Council Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Education Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Invested Reserves Planning Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Long-Range Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1989-1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Maher, Bill, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Meeting
        - Fall 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1990, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Spring 1989, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Relations with State and Local Organizations, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Resolution (Beryl Manne), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - SAA, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - SAA Distinguished Service Award, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - SAA MAC Mixer, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Valerie Gerrard Browne
      - Advertising Policy Task Force, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Archival Issues Editorial Board, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Archival Issues Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Archives Committee, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Archivist of the United States, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - ARMA/SAA Joint Committee, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Automation Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Business Meeting, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Calendar 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Calendar 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Calendar 1994, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Colorado State Archives, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Constitution and Bylaws Review Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Council Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
      - Development Coordinator, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Education Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Emeritus Membership, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Financial Policies and Practices, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Graphic Design, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Guidelines Change Task Force, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Guidelines Revisions, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Investment Advisory Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Legal Counsel, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1991, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Fall 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Fall 1993, 199-1993 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Fall 1994, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Fall 1995, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1996, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Spring 1991, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Local Arrangements Committees, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - MAC Newsletter Editor, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - MAC Newsletter Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Meeting Planning Task Force, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Sites, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Member Interest Survey, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Membership Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Minority Survey, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Minutes, Index, 1981-1991, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 22)